# Egemen Ton

# SinginGiant

Beylikduzu/Istanbul +905385022224 egementon98@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/egementon 😚 egementon.com



### Summary

Passionate programmer with physics background, fueled by love for games, 2+ years of experience building prototypes and gameplay mechanics in Unreal Engine (C++/Blueprint).

Living with the dream of making games worth the players' time and offering them unforgettable experiences, similar to the experiences I am having with my favorite games.

### **Skills**

- Game Programming
- Unreal Engine, C++, Blueprint
- Gameplay, Al, Ul, Network
- Gameplay Ability System (GAS)

### **Experience**

SinginGiant

### Unreal Engine Developer

07/2024 - NOW

I am working on a first-person cooperative tactical shooter game named "Contain" and another unannounced project, contributing to various aspects of game development.

### Gameplay & Al Programmer

02/2023 - 05/2024

### **Funverse Games**

I worked on a Battle Royale/MOBA game called "Hit and Boom" using Unreal Engine. Throughout the project, I actively contributed to various aspects, including gameplay, AI, and UI. My primary focus was on player abilities, where I was involved in developing new abilities and addressing bugs. Additionally, I worked on UI elements and enhanced my network programming skills to accommodate the multiplayer nature of the game.

One of the key highlights of my contributions to this project was the design and programming of the game's AI, where I had the freedom to create the system from scratch. These AI characters move in teams of three while staying in the zone, clearing enemy camps, engaging in fights using skills, strategically avoiding disadvantaged situations, and surviving until reaching the final zone. The resulting work received positive feedback from both players and my colleagues.

# Undergraduate Research Assistant

09/2021 - 07/2022

# ITU Nanomechanics Laboratory

I investigated the mechanical properties of graphene structures by scanning surfaces with Atomic Force Microscope.

### **Engineering Intern**

08/2020 - 09/2020

### TUBITAK - National Metrology Institute

I tested a specific machine to see if it complies with the standards.

**Portfolio** 

My website: egementon.com

**Hobbies & Activities** 

• I am a self-taught piano and guitar player who has enthusiasm for

Consistently attending the gym and

playing football to maintain a healthy

caring for animals to the best of my

• I am an animal lover, dedicated to

· Playing video games

composing music

and active lifestyle

• Reading sci-fi/fantasy books

Watching movies

### Certifications

ability

- DIGIAGE Game Development Summer Camp Attendance Certificate (1-11 September 2022)
- Learn C++ for Game Development
- Unreal Engine 5 C++ Developer: Learn C++ & Make Video Games
- Unreal Engine C++ The Ultimate **Shooter Course**
- The Ultimate Git Course with Applications in Unreal Engine

### **Education**

Physics Engineering (B.S.)

2016 - 2022

Istanbul Technical University

GPA: 3.00

Relevant Coursework: Symbolic and Numerical Techniques in Physics (C++/Matlab), Computational Analysis of Physical Systems (Python), Introduction to Programming Language (Fortran)

Thesis Title: "Exploring New Methods to Mechanically Exfoliate Graphene and Examining the Cleavage Energy of Graphite", "Applications of Atomic Force Microscopy"

### References

Lead Game Developer - Muhammed Doğru